mohankumars.com 2009-06-19

# ((:: MohanKumars.Com ::))

**:: _Privacy Policy_ ::**

 _ **Information Collection and Use:**_  
Our website's newsletter sign-up form requires users to give us their email address. Users may opt out of receiving future mailings at any time. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Any information used for providing services through MohanKumars.Com is not linked to any personally identifiable information. MohanKumars.Com may collect information from users at several different points on our web site like email id from Forum Registrations , Lyrics section, Photoshow etc.

 _ **Cookies:**_  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. Some of our business partners use cookies on our web site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

_**Log Files:**_  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the web site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

_**Sharing:**_  
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may also use third parties to provide other services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

_**Links:**_  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we at MohanKumars.Com are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our web site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. Any links posted by the visitors inside this website through Forums, or any other section, we are not responsible for any privacy practices, as it is absoultely impossible to check each and everyone's posting eventhough we try our level best to restrict any false and misuse activities.

 _ **Security:**_  
This web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and offline. 

_**Disclaimer:**_  
All content, images and files on this site are either the property of MohanKumars.Com or permission has been granted to use them. This site, [http://www.mohankumars.com](http://www.mohankumars.com/) features content (music) that is protected by copyright laws. Unless stated explicitly, all songs on this website belong to the owners of their copyrights, and may NOT be distributed without their prior consent. The songs are provided for evaluation purposes only, and you are supposed to delete them within 24 hours of the time you finished downloading them. By downloading the song(s), you agree to undertake any responsibility that is associated with the protection of their copyrights. You are encouraged to buy the original music (Audio,CD,Cassette) for the song(s). I am not aware of any copyright violation, by hosting this page. If there is any, please inform me. I will remove the links immediately. Please note this website is a personal website ONLY and no way acts as a commercial one.

 _ **Contact Information:**_  
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, or any other concerns about MohanKumars.Com, you should contact the webmaster via email at [webmaster@mohankumars.com](mailto:webmaster@mohankumars.com)
